-When I was a kid,
-Whenever I'd feel small
or lonely,
-I'd look up at the stars.
Wondered if there was life
up there.
Turns out I was looking
in the wrong direction.
When alien life
entered our world
It was from deep beneath
the pacific ocean.
A fissure between
two tectonic plates.
A portal between dimensions.
The breach.
I was fifteen
when the first Kaiju
Made land in san Francisco.
By the time tanks, jets
and missiles took it down
Six days and 35 miles later,
three cities were destroyed.
Tens of thousands
of lives were lost.
We mourned our dead,
memorialized the attack,
And moved on.
And then, only six months later,
The second attack hit manila.
The acid
factor of the Kaiju blood
Creates a toxic phenomenon
named Kaiju blue.
And then the third one hit Cabo.
And then the fourth.
And then we learned
this was not gonna stop.
This was just the beginning.
We needed a new weapon.
The world came together,
pooling its resources
And throwing aside old rivalries
For the sake
of the greater good.
To fight monsters,
we created monsters of our own.
The Jaeger program was born.
There were setbacks at first.
The neural load to interface
with a Jaeger
Proved too much
for a single pilot.
A twoPilot system
was implemented.
LeftHemisphere,
rightHemisphere pilot control.
We started winning.
Jaegers stopping Kaijus
everywhere.
But the jaegers were only
as good as their pilots.
So Jaeger pilots
turned into rock stars.
Danger turned into propaganda.
Kaijus into toys.
We got really good at it.
Winning.
Then..
then it all changed.
Gipsy danger,
report to bay 08, level a42.
Kaiju. Code name: Knifehead.
Category 3.
Yo, Yancy, wake up!
Movement in the breach.
Hey, come on!
We're being deployed.
Great. Good morning.
Mornin'.
Kaiju's a category 3..
Biggest one yet.
Code name: Knifehead.
What time is it?
2:00. Man: Go, go, go!
Move it!
A.M.?
Yep.
What do you say?
Fifth notch on the belt?
Come on, beckets.
Time for the drop.
Hey, kid.
Yeah?
Don't get cocky.
Years before,
You wouldn't have picked my
brother Yancy and I for heroes.
No chance.
Good morning, sir.
All right, let's suit up
and kick some ass!
We were never star athletes.
Never at the head of the class.
But we could hold our own
in a fight.
And it turned out
we had a unique skill:
We were drift compatible.
All right.
Data on helmet.
Data relay gel dispersing
in circuitry suit.
Good morning, Becket boys!
Tendo, what's happening,
my man?
How'd that date with Alison
go last night, Mr. Choi?
Oh, she loved me.
Her boyfriend? Not so much.
You're gonna get
your ass kicked.
A man's gotta do
what a man's gotta do, brother.
Engage drop, Mr. Choi.
Engaging drop, sir.
Marshal Pentecost on deck.
Securing the Conn pod.
Gettin' ready to drop.
Conn pod door lock secure.
Release for drop.
Gipsy danger ready
for the big drop.
Here we go.
Yeah!
Here we go!
Coupling confirmed, sir.
Engage pilotToPilot
protocol.
Engaging now.
PilotToPilot
connection protocol sequence.
Gipsy launch, bay 6.
Gipsy danger ready
and aligned, sir.
Rangers, this is
marshal stacker Pentecost.
Prepare for neural handshake.
Starting in 15 seconds.
14..13..
12, 11, 10..
Ready to step
into my head, kid?
..9, 8, 7, 6.. please, after you.
Age before beauty, old man.
PilotToPilot connection
protocol sequence..5, 4, 3..
Neural handshake initiated.
..2, 1.
The drift.
Jaeger tech.
Based on Darpa jet fighter
neural systems.
Two pilots,
mindMelding through memories
With the body
of a giant machine.
The deeper the bond..
the better you fight.
Neural handshake
strong and holding.
Right hemisphere
is calibrating.
Left hemisphere calibrating.
Proofed and transmitting.
Gentlemen, your orders are
To hold the miracle mile
off anchorage. Copy?
Copy that, sir.
Sir, there's still a civilian
vessel in the gulf..
Gentlemen, you're protecting
a city of 2 million people.
You will not risk those lives
for a boat that holds 10.
Am I clear?
Yes, sir.
Man, that's cold.
You know what I'm thinking.
I'm in your brain.
I know.
Then let's go fishing.
Here we go!
Come on, bro!
Put some muscle to it!
Worry about yourself, kiddo!
There are things
you can't fight, acts of god.
You see a hurricane coming,
you have to get out of the way.
But when you're in a Jaeger,
Suddenly, you can fight
the hurricane.
You can win.
Get 'em tied down
and go down below!
Now!
How far to the mainland?
7 miles off anchorage, sir.
But we won't even make it past
the shallows!
No, we won't!
What about that island
3 miles east?
No! No!
It's 2 miles, sir.
OOne mile, sir!
It's getting closer.
How the hell
can it be getting closer?
Kaiju.
Harder starboard!
I'm doing it as fast as I can!
Now!
Oh, god!
What the hell?
Hang on!
Ship secure.
Adjust the torque!
I'm on it.
Torque locked.
Get him. Come on.
Shoot him.
I'm on it!
Discharge reading, sir.
Plasma cannon
in the shallow shelves
7 miles off the coastal line.
Gipsy,
what the hell is going on?
Job's done, sir.
Lit it up twice.
Bagged our fifth kill.
You disobeyed a direct order!
Respectfully, sir,
We intercepted a Kaiju and
saved everyone on that boat.
Get back to your post, now!
Yes, sir.
Kaiju signature rising!
Sensor checks.
That thing's still alive, sir.
Gipsy!
We're still getting
a signature!
That Kaiju is still alive!
Grab the boat
and get out of there.
You copy?
Grab the boat
and get out of there now!
Take it, Raleigh!
I got this!
Loccent, we're hit!
Left arm's gone cold, sir.
The hull!
It went through the hull!
Raleigh, listen to me!
You need..
No! No!
Loading.
Second discharge fried
all the comms, sir.
I'm not getting any signals.
Pressure dropping!
No pressure!
No signatures, sir.
What do we do now, sir?
Now, I want you to keep
your eye on that gauge there.
Now, you know
what I'd like to find?
I'd like to find a whole ship.
That's what I'd like to find.
Wait, wait!
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
Wait!
Right there, right there!
Dig!
Hey, what is it?
It's just an old toy.
We never find anything good.
Listen.
Jeez!
Oh, my god.
Stay here!
Mister?
Can I help?
Yancy.
Run!
Get help, fast!
It's gonna be all right.
The Kaiju are learning
our defenses.
They're adapting.
Evolving.
And we're losing jaegers faster
than we can build them.
Lima.
Seattle.
Vladivostok.
Category 4 Kaijus are now
coming through the breach.
I think even you can see,
marshal,
This is no longer
a sound strategy.
The frequency of the attacks
has increased.
The jaegers are not
the most viable
Line of defense anymore.
I am aware.
Those are my rangers that die
every time a Jaeger falls,
Which is why I'm asking you
for one last chance..
Excuse me, marshal.
Excuse me!
..one final assault with
everything we've got. Listen to me.
The Jaeger program
is dead, marshal.
On the other hand,
The coastal wall program
is a promising option.
The world appreciates
All that you and your men
have done,
But it's over.
We will authorize you
To take all remaining jaegers
Hong Kong.
We're prepared to fund you
for the next eight months
While the coastal wall
is completed.
After that, you will receive
no further support.
You have your answer, marshal.
So that's it?
It's over?
Suits and ties, flashy smiles.
That's all they are, stacker.
We don't need 'em.
Ration cards, guys!
Come on, come on!
Let's go!
Now, I got good news
and I got bad news, fellas.
Which one you wanna hear first?
Bad news!
Three guys died yesterday
working the top of the wall.
What's the good news?
The good news is,
I got three new job openings.
Top of the wall.
Okay, who wants to work?
Who wants to eat?
Come on!
I am here in Sydney,
where earlier today,
Yet another Kaiju attack
took place.
The Kaiju,
an enormous category 4,
Broke through the coastal wall
in less than an hour.
The wall of life
had been deemed unbreachable
By its builders.
Why the hell are we even
buildin' this thing?
The creature entered the city
through Sydney cove.
That.. That thing
Went through the wall like it was nothing.
Ironically, it was
The recently decommissioned
Jaeger, striker eureka,
Piloted by Herc
and chuck Hansen,
That finally took
the beast down.
Look, they decommissioned
The Jaeger program
because of mediocre pilots.
It's that simple.
That's striker eureka's
tenth kill to date.
It's a new record.
And you're still
going to Hong Kong,
Even at a time like this?
Well, orders are orders.
What else am I supposed to do?
Come on, mate.
Chuck Hansen, one of
the pilots of striker eureka,
The Jaeger that took down
the Kaiju.
Mr. Becket.
Marshal.
Looking sharp.
Long time.
Five years, four months.
Can I have a word?
Attention,
all zone three welders.
Step into my office, marshal.
Took me a while to find you.
Anchorage, Sheldon point,
Nome..
Yeah, a man in my position
travels with the wall,
Chasing shifts
to make a livin'.
What do you want?
I've spent the last six months
Activating everything
I can get my hands on.
There's an old Jaeger,
a mark 3.
You may know it.
It needs a pilot.
I'm guessing I wasn't
your first choice.
You a my first choice.
All the other mark 3 pilots
are dead.
Look..
I can't have anyone else
in my head again.
I'm done.
I was still connected
to my brother when he died.
I can't go through that again,
man, I'm sorry.
Haven't you heard,
Mr. Becket?
The world is coming to an end.
So where would you rather die?!
Here, or in a Jaeger?!
Mr. Becket,
this is Mako Mori.
One of our brightest.
Also in charge of the mark 3
restoration program.
She personally handpicked
your copilot candidates.
Hey.
At ease.
We will tour the facility first
And then miss Mori will show you
to your Jaeger, Mr. Becket.
Wait for us, please!
Hold the door, please!
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you.
Stay back! Kaiju specimens
are extremely rare,
So look
but don't touch, please.
Mr. Becket,
this is our research team.
Dr. Gottlieb
and dr. Geiszler.
Oh, no, call me newt.
Only my mother calls me doctor.
Hermann, these are human beings.
Why don't you say hello?
I have asked you not to refer to
me by my first name around others.
I am a doctor with over 10 years
decorated experience..
Oh, no, yes.
I have ten.. 10 years of experience, man.
I'm very sorry.
Oh, please.
Who is that, Yamarashi?
Oh, this little Kaiju?
Yeah, you got a good eye.
My brother and I
took him down in 2017.
You know he was one of
the biggest category 3s ever?
He was 2,500 tons of awesome.
Or awful. You know,
whatever you wanna call it.
Yes, please excuse him.
He's a Kaiju groupie.
He loves..
Shut up, Hermann,
I don't love them, okay?
I study them.
And unlike most people,
I wanna see one alive
and up close one day.
Trust me, you don't want to.
So that's your
research division?
Things have changed.
We're not an army anymore,
Mr. Becket.
We're the resistance.
Welcome to the shatterdome.
War clock.
We reset it
after every Kaiju attack.
Keeps everyone focused.
The frequency of attacks
is accelerating.
How long till the next reset?
A week, if we're lucky.
My experts believe there'll be
a Kaiju attack
Even before that.
This complex used to
lodge 30 jaegers
In five bays
just like this one.
Now we only have
four jaegers left.
I didn't know it was this bad.
It is that bad.
Crimson typhoon, china.
One of the greatest.
Assembled in Changzhou.
Full titanium core, no alloys.
Fifty diesel engines
per muscle strand.
Deadly, precise fighter.
She's piloted
by the wei tang brothers.
Triplets.
Local lads.
They've successfully defended
Hong Kong port seven times.
They use
the thundercloud formation.
Oh, yeah.
TripleArm technique.
Very effective.
That tank,
last of the t90s.
Cherno alpha.
First generation mark 1.
The heaviest and oldest Jaeger
in the service.
But make no mistake, Mr. Becket,
it's a brutal war machine.
And those two,
Sasha and Alexis Kaidanovksy.
Yeah, I've heard of 'em.
Perimeter patrol,
Siberian wall.
On thei watch it stayed
unbreached for six years.
Six years.
Herc! Chuck!
Gentlemen,
welcome to Hong Kong!
Wait here.
Max!
Come here!
Remember me?
Don't drool all over miss Mori.
Hi.
Sees a pretty girl
and he gets all wound up.
Raleigh,
this is Hercules Hansen,
An old friend
from the mark 1 glory days.
I know you, mate.
We rode together before.
We did, sir. Six years ago.
My brother and I.
It was a three Jaeger team drop.
That's right. Manila.
Sorry about your brother.
Thank you, sir.
Herc and his son chuck'll
be runnin' point
Usin' striker eureka.
Fastest Jaeger in the world.
First and last of the mark 5s.
Australia decommissioned it
a day before the Sydney attack.
Yeah, it was lucky we were still around.
Yep.
Now it's runnin' point for us.
Wait, running point on what?
You haven't told me
what I'm doing here yet.
We're going for the breach,
Mr. Becket.
We're gonna strap a 2,400 pound
Thermonuclear warhead
to striker's back.
Detonate an equivalent of
1.2 million tons of TNT,
And you and two other Jaegers'll
be runnin' defense for them.
Thought we were the resistance.
Where'd you get something
that big?
See the Russians back there?
They can get us anything.
Herc, shall we?
Good to have you back.
Thank you, sir.
I'll show you
to your Jaeger now.
Miss Mori,
will you give me a minute?
Marshal!
Sir, we've hit
the breach before.
It doesn't work.
Nothing goes through.
What's changed?
I've got a plan.
I need you ready.
That's all.
Let's go, Herc!
Max, come here!
Crew 17, please report
to the fifth floor.
Zero minus two.
Xy minus two.
REQ.
In the beginning,
The Kaiju attacks
were spaced by 24 weeks.
Then twelve, then six,
then every two weeks.
The last one in Sydney
was a week.
In four days, we could be seeing
a Kaiju every eight hours
Until they are coming
every four minutes.
Marshal, we should witness
a double event
Within seven days.
Mr. Gottlieb,
I'm to drop a 2,400 pound
thermonuclear bomb.
I need more than a prediction.
Well, uh,
that's a problem, then
Because see, he actually
Can't give you anything more
than a prediction.
No Kaiju entrails over my side
of the room.
You know the rules.
Every bloody day.
It's incessant.
Gents! On point.
Numbers do not lie.
Politics and poetry,
promises, these are lies.
Numbers are as close as we get
to the handwriting of god.
What?
Would you give me a moment?
There will be a double event
And then,
shortly thereafter, three.
And then four.
And then we're dead.
I get it.
Alas.
This is where
the good news comes.
Here is our universe,
And here is theirs.
And this is what we call
"the throat,"
The passage between
the breach and us.
We know that it's atomic
in nature.
I predict that
the increased traffic
Will force the breach
to stabilize
And remain open long enough
To get the device through..
and collapse its structure.
Yeah, and that's where
I gotta chime in
Because, really,
I wouldn't wanna go in there
With that limited amount
of information.
Newton,
don't embarrass yourself.
That's what I was tryin' to say.
Just hear me out for a second.
Give me a second, please.
Why do we judge the Kaiju
on a category system?
It's because each one is completely
different from the next, right?
You see what I'm saying? One looks like
a shark and one looks like a fish..
Dr. Geiszler.
Just get to the point.
Yes.
The point is I don't think
They're all completely different
after all.
These are some samples
I collected, all right?
Now, this one here
was harvested in Sydney.
And this was harvested
in manila.
6 years ago.
They have the same exact DNA.
They're clones.
And this is the point where
he goes completely crazy.
There's so much more to
the Kaiju than we understand.
And we've really only
scratched the surface.
This is a piece
of a Kaiju's brain.
Now, unfortunately,
it's damaged.
It's a little bit weak.
But it's still alive.
Now, I think I can tap into it
Using the same technology
That allows the two Jaeger
pilots to share a neural bridge.
Now, think about that.
I could tell you exactly
How to get through
the breach yourselves.
You're suggesting that we
initiate a drift with a Kaiju?
No, no. No, no. Not like
a whole Kaiju, you know,
Just a tiny piece of its brain.
The neural surge would be
too much for the human brain.
I agree.
I don't agree.
Gottlieb, I'd like your data
on my desk asap.
Sir.
No, but his is so..
Thank you, newt.
Guys, now, this is
the most amazing thing..
Newton, I know that you're
desperate to be right
So you've not wasted your life
being a Kaiju groupie,
But it's not going to work.
It is going to work, Hermann.
And I'll tell you
something else.
Fortune favors the brave, dude.
You heard them.
They won't give you
the equipment
And even if they did,
you'd kill yourself.
Well, I'd be a rock star.
There she is.
Oh, my god.
Look at her.
Gipsy danger.
God, it's so beautiful.
She looks like new.
Better than new.
She has a doubleCore
nuclear reactor.
She's one of a kind now.
She always was.
How do you like
your ride, Becket boy?
Solid iron hull, no alloys.
Forty engine blocks
per muscle strands.
HyperTorque driver
for every limb
And a new fluid synapse system.
Come here.
Tendo.
It's good to see you, buddy.
It's good
to see you too, brother.
It's just like old times.
So what's your story?
Restoring old jaegers,
Showing hasBeens
like me around.
That can't be it.
You a pilot?
No. No yet.
But I wanna be one,
more than anything.
What's your simulator score?
51 drops, 51 kills.
Wow, that's amazing.
But you're not one of
the candidates tomorrow?
I am not.
The marshal has his reasons.
Yeah, he always does,
doesn't he?
But with 51 kills, I can't
imagine what they could be.
I hope you approve
of my choices.
I've studied your fighting
techniques and strategy.
Even.. Alaska.
And what do you think?
I think you're unpredictable.
You have a habit of deviating
From standard
combat techniques.
You take risks and injure
yourself and your crew.
I don't think you're the right
man for this mission.
Wow.
Thank you for your honesty.
You might be right.
But one day,
when you're a pilot,
You're gonna see that in combat
you make decisions.
And you have to live
with the consequences.
That's what I'm trying to do.
The candidates are ready.
We will commence the trials
immediately, sir.
Good.
But there is one thing.
We.. Mako,
we have talked about this.
We will not be talking
about it again.
Hm?
You promised me.
Mako.
Vengeance is like
an open wound.
You cannot take that level
of emotion into the drift.
For my family, I need..
Raleigh.
Come sit with us.
Oh, I'm okay, thank you.
Ah, come on, there's plenty
of room at our table.
I haven't seen bread in awhile.
Hong Kong.
Beauty of an open port,
no rationing.
We've got potatoes, peas,
sweet beans, decent meat loaf.
Pass the potatoes.
Raleigh, this is my son, chuck.
He's my copilot now.
He's more my copilot,
right, dad?
So you're the guy, eh?
You're the guy who's gonna run
defense for me
In that old rust bucket
of yours?
That's the plan.
Good.
So when was the last time
you jockeyed, ray?
About five years ago.
What have you been doin'
for five years?
Something pretty important,
I reckon.
I was in construction.
Oh, wow, that's great.
I mean, that's really useful.
Uh, you know,
we get into a fight,
You can build our way
out of it, eh, ray?
It's Raleigh.
Whatever.
Look, you're Pentecost's
bright idea.
My old man,
he seems to like you,
But it's guys like you who
brought down the Jaeger program.
To me, you're dead weight.
You slow me down,
I'm gonna drop you
like a sack of Kaiju shit.
I'll see you around, Raleigh.
Come, max.
You can blame me for that one.
I've raised him on my own.
He's a smart kid,
but I never knew
Whether to give him a hug
or a kick in the ass.
With respect, sir..
I'm pretty sure
which one he needs.
4 points to zero.
4 points to 1.
4 points to 2.
Okay, what?
You don't like 'em?
I thought you selected
them personally.
Excuse me?
Every time a match ends
You make this little gesture,
Like you're critical
of their performance.
It's not their performance,
it's yours.
Your gambit.
You could have taken all of them
two moves earlier.
You think so?
I know so.
Can we change this up?
How 'bout we give her a shot?
Yeah!
No.
We stick to the cadet list
we have, ranger.
Only candidates
with drift compatibility..
Which I have, marshal.
Mako, this is not only about
a neural connection.
It's also about
a physical compatibility.
What's the matter, marshal?
Don't think your brightest can
cut it in the ring with me?
Go.
Four strikes marks a win.
Remember,
it's about compatibility.
It's a dialogue, not a fight.
But I'm not gonna dial down
my moves.
Okay.
Then neither will I.
10.
11.
21.
Concentrate.
22.
Better watch it.
32.
MoriSan.
Enough.
I've seen what I need to see.
Me too.
She's my copilot.
That's not going to work.
Why not?
Because I said so,
Mr. Becket.
I made my decision.
Report to the shatterdome
in two hours
And find out
who your copilot will be.
Mako.
What was all that about?
I mean, I'm not crazy.
You felt it, right?
We are drift compatible.
Thank you for standing up
for me.
But there is nothing
to talk about.
That's my room.
Excuse me.
I mean, come on. I thought
you wanted to be a pilot.
Mako,
this is worth fighting for.
We don't have to just obey him.
It's not obedience,
Mr. Becket.
It's respect.
Would you at least tell me
what his problem is?
In the wake
of the Sydney incident,
Which showed
the ineffective nature
Of the wall of life program,
Many are questioning
the government's motives
And wondering why the Jaeger
program has been discontinued.
Riots have erupted
along the coastlines
Of several pan pacific cities.
We have now relocated
millions of civilians
And supplies 300 miles inland
to the safe zones.
Safe zones?
For the rich and powerful?
What about the rest of us?
Yeah, answer the question.
I believe the wall of life
Is still our best option
at this time.
And that's all I'm gonna say
on the matter.
Than.. Thank you.
Kaiju/human drift experiment,
take one.
The, uh.. The brain segment
is the frontal lobe.
Um, chances are..
the segment's far too damaged
to drift with.
Hermann, if you're
listening to this,
Well, I'm either alive
And I've proven
what I've just done works..
in which case, ha, I won.
Or I'm dead and I'd like you to
know that it's all your fault.
It really is, you know.
You drove me to this.
In which case, ha, I also won.
Sort of.
I'm going in in three..
two..
one.
Hah!
Newton.
Newton!
What have you done?
Gipsy danger neural test
Commencing in 20 minutes.
Gipsy danger neural test commencing
in 20 minutes.
Mm.
May I come in, Mako?
All pilots report to mess hall.
A long time ago,
I made you a promise.
These transmitters
are nonOperative.
I need them replaced.
Setting harness for test mode.
Waiting for second pilot.
Two pilots on board.
I'm gonna take this side
if you don't mind.
My left arm's kinda shot.
Sure.
Are you gonna say anything?
No point.
In five minutes you're
gonna be inside my head.
You look good.
Pilots on board
and ready to connect.
Prepare for neural handshake.
Initiating neural handshake.
We're not in
the simulator now, Mako.
Remember,
don't chase the rabbit.
Random access
brain impulse triggers.
Memories.
Just let 'em flow,
don't latch on.
Tune 'em out.
Stay in the drift.
The drift is silence.
Neural interface drift
initiated.
Look, Raleigh!
Over there!
Mama!
Raleigh, listen to me!
Right hemisphere calibrated.
Left hemisphere calibrated.
Ready to activate the Jaeger.
Okay, gipsy.
Lining up nicely.
Better get ready.
Pilot to Jaeger connection
complete.
Marshal!
I need to talk to you.
Not now, Mr. Gottlieb.
I'm sure you can appreciate
How important
this moment is to me.
Newton created a neural bridge
From garbage
and drifted with a Kaiju.
I found him prone,
and he's sort of dazed.
I don't exactly know
what to do.
I told you it would work.
Yes, you did.
Well, what'd you see?
You know, it was only
a fragment of a brain,
So really all I was able to get
was, like, a series
Of, uh, images or..
Or impressions. You know?
Like when you blink your eyes
over and over and over again
All you really see
are, like, frames.
Um, it was emotional in the..
Newton, Newton.
Okay, Newton.
It was so..
Newton, look at me.
Now I want you to take your time
and be very specific.
Okay.
Well, I don't feel like
They're just following some sort
of animalistic urge,
You know, just hunting
and gathering.
And I think they're attacking us
under orders.
That's impossible.
Is that impossible?
It's impossible.
Because.. You know what?
Why don't you drift with a Kaiju?!
You! Shut up!
Yes, sir.
You, keep talking.
These beings, these masters,
they're colonists.
They overtake worlds.
They just..
They just consume them
and then..
Then, they move on to the next.
And they've been here before
in sort of a trial run.
It was the dinosaurs.
But the atmosphere
wasn't conducive, right?
So they waited it out.
And they waited it out.
And now, you know,
with ozone depletion,
And carbon monoxide,
polluted waters..
Well, we've practically
terraformed it for them.
'Cause now they're coming back,
and it's perfect.
See, the first wave,
that was just the hounds.
Categories 1 through 4,
it was nothing.
Their sole purpose was to aim
for the populated areas
And take out
the vermin.. Us!
The second wave,
that is the exterminators.
And they will finish the job.
And then, the new tenants
will take possession.
See, the reason that I found
the identical DNA
In the two separate Kaiju organs
is because they are grown!
Newton,
I need you to do it again.
I need more information.
Wh..? I can't..
I can't do it again.
II mean,
not unless you have
A fresh Kaiju brain
lying around.
Do you?
Pretty impressive.
Yeah, he remembers
how to turn it on.
Oi, show some respect.
When his brother died,
He got the Jaeger back to shore
on his own.
I've known one other pilot's
been able to do that.
Now, there are
certain individuals
Whose business
is the preservation
And exploitation
of Kaiju remains.
Yeah, right, black market
dealers, right?
Yep. They're in and out
in a matter of hours.
They neutralize the acidic
factor of the blood,
And they harvest
what they need.
Now, this guy,
this is Hannibal Chau.
He runs the Kaiju black market
here in Asia.
When our funding ran out,
We turned to him for help,
and in return,
I gave him exclusive rights
To all Kaiju remains
in the region.
You did that?
Last days of war, gentlemen.
Go to the corner of fong
and tull.
Show them that card.
Look for that symbol.
And a word to the wise,
do not trust him.
Calibration complete.
The hull!
It went through the hull!
Raleigh, listen to me!
You need..
Pilot out of alignment.
Both out of alignment.
Both of them?
Both of them.
Gipsy, gipsy!
You're out of alignment!
You are both out of alignment.
I'm okay.
Just let me control it.
Pilot two, out of alignment.
You're stabilizing.
But Mako is way out.
Mako.
She's starting to chase the rabbit!
Mako, don't get stuck
in a memory.
Stay with me.
Stay in the now.
Don't engage in a memory.
Mako.
Mako!
Listen to me.
Mako?
Mama!
Mako.
This is just a memory.
None of this is real.
Weapons system engaged.
Plasma cannon powering up.
Oh, no.
Weapon system engaged!
Go to failSafe!
FailSafe not responding.
There's a problem
with the neural blocker!
Her connection's
way too strong!
Fully charged.
Mako!
Mako, listen to me.
This is just a memory.
None of it is real.
The power line!
Get the main power line!
Take them offline!
I just did.
Weapon system disengaged.
Mako!
Neural bridge exercise invalid.
It's okay.
Drift sequence terminated.
Would you like to try again?
Hello.
PssPsst.
You looking for
some Kaiju bone powder?
SSome bone..?
Some bone powder?
Uh, no, why would I want that?
Male potency.
I take it myself.
I see.
Uh, no, thank you.
I'm looking for Hannibal Chau.
Come.
Hannibal Chau, huh?
Good luck.
Oh, my god!
Oh, my god,
this place is heaven!
That's a lymph gland
from a category 2!
And what are you
working on here?
Is this a cuticle?
In mint condition?
Is that a Kaiju skin parasite?
I've never seen them
alive before!
TheyThey usually die
as soon as the Kaiju falls!
I thought you couldn't
keep them alive!
You can if you soak
'em in ammonia.
What do you want?
I'm looking for Hannibal Chau.
I was told he was here.
Who wants to know?
I really can't say.
Aah! Aah!
Stacker Pentecost sent me!
Oh, that's great.
That's real great.
So I take it
you're Hannibal Chau, right?
You like the name?
I took it from, uh..
my favorite
historical character
And my secondFavorite Szechuan
restaurant in Brooklyn.
Now tell me what you want,
Before I gut you like a pig
and feed you to the skin louse.
She can't control her drift,
And he went out of phase first!
We all know what happened.
We can't afford mistakes,
the Kaiju keep evolving,
They keep kicking our asses!
He's a hasBeen,
she's a rookie.
I don't want them protecting
my bomb run, sir.
You need to watch your tone,
Mr. Hansen.
Hey, stay there.
Give me a moment.
You two are a goddamn disgrace.
You're gonna get us all killed,
I want to come back
from this mission
'Cause I quite like my life.
So why don't you just do us all
a favor and disappear?
It's the only thing
you're good at.
Stop! Now!
Yeah, that's right.
You just hold back
your little girlfriend.
One of you bitches
needs a leash.
Apologize to her.
Screw you.
Aah!
I said apologize to her.
Hey!
Hey! Enough!
What's going on?
On your feet, both of you!
Becket, Mori,
into my office, now.
No, we aren't finished!
Hey! Hey! This is over!
You're a ranger, for Chrissake.
Why don't you start
acting like one?
I went out of phase first.
It was my mistake.
No.
I should have never let you two
in the same machine.
So, what?
You're grounding us?
Not you.
Permission
to be dismissed, sir.
Permission granted, miss Mori.
Mako.
Sir, what are you doing?
She is the strongest
candidate by far.
What other options do we have?
Huh? Tell me!
Do not let my calm demeanor
fool you, ranger!
Now is not a good moment
for your insubordination!
Mako is too inexperienced
To rein in her memories
during combat.
That's not why
you grounded her.
I was in her memories.
I saw everything.
I don't care
what you think you saw.
I know what she means to you.
I saw it! I..
Hey! Hey!
This conversation is over.
Marshal.
Marshal, can we just talk
about this for one second?!
You rescued her.
You raised her.
You're not protecting her now.
You are holding her back.
Don't you ever touch me again.
Now, you have no idea
who the hell I am
Or where I've come from,
And I'm not about to tell you
my whole life story.
All I need to be to you
and everybody in this dome
Is a fixed point.
The last man standing.
I do not need your sympathy
or your admiration.
All I need is your compliance
and your fighting skills.
And if I can't get that,
Then you can go back
to the wall
That I found you crawling on.
Do I make myself clear?
Yes, sir.
Good.
I'm sorry.
I should've warned you.
First drifts are rough.
But you weren't just tapping
into my memories.
You were tapping
into my brother's too.
When Yancy was taken,
we were still connected.
I felt his fear, his pain,
His helplessness, and then..
he was gone.
I felt it.
I know.
You know, you live in someone
else's head for so long
The hardest part to deal with
is the silence.
To let someone else in,
to really connect,
You have to trust them.
And today the drift was strong.
Her heart.
When's the last time
you saw it?
Not in a long time.
Movement in the breach.
Double event.
Two signatures.
Dilation indicator, category 4.
Excuse me.
The breach
was exposed at 2300 hours.
We have two signatures,
both category 4s.
Otachi and leatherback.
They'll reach Hong Kong
within the hour.
Evacuate the city.
Shut down the bridges.
I want every single civilian
in a refuge right now.
Crimson typhoon, cherno alpha,
I want you to frontline
the harbor.
Stay on the miracle mile.
Striker,
I want you to stay back,
Look after the coastline.
We cannot afford to lose you,
So only engage
as a final option.
Yes, sir!
You two.
You stay put.
Let's go!
Loccent, striker's got the ball
and we're on the roll.
Loccent.. near positions
and awaiting your orders.
Remain in the miracle mile.
Engage at your discretion.
Guys, keep your eyes open.
These category 4s are
the biggest we've ever seen,
Both in size and weight.
Cherno alpha
reaching target zone.
Disengaging transport.
Cherno alpha in position.
Miracle mile.
Cherno alpha
holding the coastline.
Beacon is on.
Look at 'em.
They believe the Kaiju
are sent from heaven.
That the gods are expressing
their displeasure
With our behavior.
The silly bastards.
And what do you believe?
Well..
I believe that Kaiju bone powder
is 500 bucks a pound.
What do you want?
I need to access a Kaiju brain.
Completely intact.
No, no, no.
The skull plate is so dense
That by the time
you drill into it..
The brain's rotted away.
But I'm talking about
the secondary brain.
Now we both know
that the Kaiju are so large
They need two brains to move
around, like a dinosaur.
I want to get my hands on that.
Mm.
What the hell do you want
a secondary brain for, anyway?
I mean, every part
of the Kaiju sells.
Cartilage, spleen, liver.
Even the crap!
One cubic meter of crap
Has enough phosphorous in it
to fertilize a whole field!
But the brain..
too much ammonia.
So what's the deal,
little fella?
Well, that's classified.
So I couldn't tell you.
Even if I wanted to.
Mm.
But it is pretty cool.
So I might tell you.
I'm gonna tell you.
I figured out how to drift
with a Kaiju.
Are you funnin' me, son?
It's fascinating
how their minds work.
Every single Kaiju,
his mind's connected.
The species has like a..
Like a hive mind.
Holy Jesus.
You've gone and done it,
haven't you?
I did it a little bit, yeah.
You goddamn moron.
Loccent! Typhoon and alpha
are in trouble.
We're movin' in!
You are to hold your ground.
Do not engage.
We need you to carry that bomb.
Do you copy?
Jesus, we can't just sit here
and watch 'em die. Come on!
Ah, screw this.
Loccent, we're movin' in now!
Cherno alpha,
we've been hit with some type of acid!
Come on!
Hull has been compromised.
We need backup immediately!
Just hold on, cherno!
We're on our way!
Our power move!
Yeah!
We just lost cherno, sir.
Engaging air missiles!
What's going on?
What happened?
The blast. It jumbled all the
jaegers' electrical circuits.
What the hell was that?
Loccent!
I've never seen that before.
They're adapting.
This isn't a defense mechanism,
it's a weapon!
Get me striker!
Nothing, sir.
The mark 5's digital's fried.
It'll take me two hours
to reroute the auxiliary.
All the jaegers,
they're digital!
Not all of them, marshal.
Gipsy's analog.
Nuclear.
We got two Kaijus.
We gotta get out.
Hang on a second. Excuse me.
WhWhat's going on?
There are two goddamn Kaiju
Headed straight
for Hong Kong city.
No, no, no. That's not possible.
There's never been two before.
Well, maybe that's 'cause
Nobody ever drifted with one
before, eh, genius?!
When Jaeger pilots drift,
it's a twoWay street.
A bridge, right?
Of course. Yes!
It sets up a connection.
Both ways!
"A hive mentality," you said!
Maybe those Kaiju
are tryin' to find you.
What.. What're
we gonna do?
I'm gonna wait out
this shitstorm
In my own private Kaiju bunker.
But you are going
to a public refuge.
I tried it once.
Once.
Now get the hell outta here.
Excuse me!
Aah!
Move! Move!
I'm a doctor! I'm a doctor!
Okay, hold on.
Let me in.
Okay, I'm a doctor.
Okay, let me in, I'm a doctor.
Please proceed immediately
to your antiKaiju refuge.
There's no emergency power.
We gotta bail.
I'm gonna try somethin' else.
No!
Don't disengage!
Aah! My arm!
Hey! Come on!
Get on your feet, old man!
Don't call me that!
He's right outside.
We gotta get outta here now!
We're not goin' anywhere!
Now you and I
are the only thing
Standin' between
that ugly bastard
And a city of 2 million people.
Now we have a choice here.
We either sit and wait
Or we take these flare guns
And do something really stupid.
How's your arm?
Ah, just give me the gun.
Hey, you!
I think we just pissed it off!
All right, Mako.
Get ready, this is for real!
Yeah!
Come on, gipsy!
Kick his ass!
Come on! Let's do this!
Together!
Elbow rocket!
Now!
Aah!
Hang on, Mako!
Plasma cannon, now!
Plasma cannon engaged.
Empty the clip!
Wait.
I think this guy's dead.
But let's check for a pulse.
Okay.
No pulse.
He stopped right above us.
Oh, my god.
This isn't a refuge. This is..
This is a buffet line!
He knows I'm here.
He knows I'm here!
He knows we're all here!
No, you don't understand,
he's trying to get me!
He knows I'm here
and he's trying to get me!
What was that?
What did you say?!
What was she saying?!
I gotta get out of here!
Let me out of here!
I got..
Ah, come on!
Those were expensive glasses.
This is the worst.
Torque engaged.
I can't pinpoint it.
It's movin' quick.
Keep your eyes open.
Choppers,
do you have a visual? Over.
Come on!
I'll hold it!
Vent the coolant
on the left flank!
Coolant venting.
Co2 purge.
Venting coolant.
Atmosphere loss in progress.
Temperature's droppin'!
We're losing oxygen!
Both plasma cannons are shot.
We're out of options, Mako.
Sword deployment.
Altitude actuation
offBalance.
50,000 feet to ground contact.
Look, there!
Altitude loss critical.
40,000 feet.
Gipsy, listen to me!
Loosen all the shock absorbers,
Use your gyroscope as balance
and ball up!
It's your only chance!
20,000 feet.
Fuel purge!
Now!
Impact alert.
We're comin' in too fast.
Brace for impact, ma..
Mako, talk to me.
Mako, you okay?
Yeah.
You?
Go to dr. Geiszler now!
Yes, sir!
I want the two remaining jaegers
back to 100% functionality.
Yes, sir!
We're gonna harvest
The skin,
the talons and the wing.
Germans are gonna go nuts
for that stuff.
Let me see that map.
Here is where the Kaiju fell,
Here's where we concentrate
our efforts.
We'll get it, boss.
Right.
Hey!
Okay, guess who's back,
you oneEyed bitch?
And you owe me a Kaiju brain.
Raleigh!
My kid'd never admit it..
but he's grateful.
We both are.
Mr. Becket!
Miss Mori!
In all of my years fighting..
I've never seen anything
like that.
Well done.
Proud of you.
Proud of us all.
But..
as harsh as it sounds,
there is no time to celebrate.
We lost two crews.
No time to grieve.
Reset that clock.
Reset the clock.
I still can't believe
what you did to me.
I mean, I coulda been eaten.
Well, that was definitely
the plan.
Lucky for you, that didn't
become necessary, huh?
Okay. Thank you so much.
You're so kind.
I really appreciate
all of this.
But now do you mind tellin' me
exactly what is taking so long
For your workers
to get that brain?
Well, they pump the cavity
full of co2,
Just like in any other
laparoscopic surgery.
Okay, yes, obviously,
The co2's gonna delay
the acidic reaction, yes.
And it allows us to harvest.
But our boys need oxygen pumped
into their suits.
They move slow.
What's goin' on in there, boys?
We've reached..
The upper pelvic area.
Moving to the 25th vertebra.
Shit.
Even through the suit, boss,
It smells like dead catfish
in here.
Boss.
The secondary brain..
is damage.
Oh.
It's ruin. Destroy.
Bitch!
How could they screw that up?!
Wait. Wait.
What was that?
Did he say "wait"?
Why wait?
Do you hear that?
It's like a heartbeat.
Oh, my god.
Oh, my god, this can't be.
Hold on a second.
Hey!
Let me have that!
Shh, shh!
Listen, listen!
Listen to this.
It's pregnant.
No, no!
Please.
No! No.
I knew it.
Aah!
Gone.
His lungs weren't fully formed.
Umbilical cord
tied around his neck.
No way he could survive
outside the womb
For more than a minute.
One look, that's all I needed.
I knew he wouldn't make it.
Ugly little bastard.
Anyway, I woulda..
Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah!
Huh.
How sick are you?
And why didn't you tell me?
Ah.
What's to tell?
You know, them mark 1s,
We scraped them bad boys
together in 14 months.
Last thing we were thinking
about was radiation shielding.
I ran nearly a dozen missions.
I stayed under
the medical radar for awhile
But the last time I jockeyed
was Tokyo.
I finished the fight solo,
but for three hours..
I burned.
They warned me if I ever stepped
foot into a Jaeger again,
The toll would be too much.
You and I are the only two
that ever ran solo combat.
That's why I brought you here.
What is it?
Sir, it's happening.
I just got two signatures
With unprecedented dilation,
40Meter spikes.
What category?
Checking the ratios,
category four.
Where're they headed?
That's the thing,
they're not headin' anywhere.
They're hovering
just above the breach.
It's.. It's like they're
protecting it or something.
All right, gipsy, striker,
on deck.
Sir, Herc cannot ride.
His arm..
You heard me.
Two signatures.
Two?! There are..
There are two Kaiju signatures
in the breach,
Not three like I predicted?!
Hermann! I haven't exactly had
a very good day, okay?!
I got about 5 minutes..
should be three Kaijus.
..before brain death
occurs here!
I don't wanna spend it talking
about your theories!
This is all wrong!
There should be three Kaijus
coming through, not two!
There should be three
and there's two?
I'm sorry, it hurts to be wrong,
doesn't it, Hermann?
I am not wrong, but there is something
here that we don't understand.
Okay. Hermann, hopefully
we can argue about any mistakes
You made in your predictive
model in the future!
But in the meantime,
The neural interface
is way off the charts!
If you want to help,
help with that!
Newton, I am not wrong.
There is only one way
to make sure..
and that is to do this..
together.
I'll go with you.
That's what
the Jaeger pilots do,
Share the neural load.
You're serious?
You.. You would do that for me?
Or you would do that with me?
Well, with worldwide destruction
a certain alternative..
do I really have a choice?
"We're gonna own this bad boy!"
By Jove, we are going to own
this thing for sure!
Oi, Tendo.
Tendo!
You're not suited up.
Yeah, I'm aware of that, Elvis.
I need to know what's going on.
He said suit up, so suit up.
Tendo, I can't pilot striker
on my own, now, can I?!
Dad's hurt, so who's gonna
be my copilot?
I don't remember it
being so tight.
Getting back into that Jaeger
will kill you.
Not gettin' into one
would kill us all.
Listen, you are a brave girl.
I'm so lucky
to have seen you grow.
But if I'm going to do this..
I need you to protect me.
Can you do that?
Hey.
Everyone, listen up!
Today..
today..
at the edge of our hope..
at the end of our time..
we have chosen not only
to believe in ourselves,
But in each other.
Today there's not a man
nor woman in here
That shall stand alone.
Not today.
Today we face the monsters
that are at our door
And bring the fight to them!
Today we are canceling
the apocalypse!
Go to the safety zone
right now.
Hey, marshal!
You know,
that was a great speech,
But how exactly are you and I
Supposed to match up in there?
I carry nothing into the drift.
No memories, no fear.
No rank.
And as for you..
well, you're easy.
You're an egotistical jerk
with daddy issues.
A simple puzzle I solved
on day one.
But you are
your father's son..
so we'll drift just fine.
Works for me.
Hey, now.
When you drift with someone,
You feel like there's nothing
to talk about.
I just don't want to regret
All the things
that I never said out loud.
Don't.
You don't need to.
I know them all.
I always have.
Hey.
Hey, handsome.
Oh, I'm gonna miss you.
You look after him for me.
Stacker.
That's my son you got there.
My son.
You know, Mako, all those years
I spent livin' in the past,
I never really thought
about the future.
Until now.
I never did have
very good timing.
You ready for this?
Oh, yes, yes.
Initiating neural
handshake in 5..
4, 3, 2, 1.
Are you okay?
Yes, of course.
I'm completely fine.
The drift.
You saw it?
Yeah.
Did you?
Listen, we have to warn them.
The jaegers..
The breach.. The plan..
It's not going to work.
Disengaging transport.
Loccent, all ports sealed.
Ready to submerge.
All ports sealed.
Both neural handshakes at 100%.
Neural handshake
confirmed, sir.
Two actives still in circle
formation in the Guam quadrant.
Scunner, Raiju.
Both category 4.
Roger that.
Half a mile to
the ocean cliff, we jump!
It's 3,000 meters
to the breach.
Half a mile?! I can't even see
a damn inch ahead!
How are we supposed
to deliver the bomb?
Visibility's zero.
Switching to instruments now.
Sir!
Gipsy, you have movement
on your right. Three o'clock!
Three o'clock!
100 feet radius, clear.
Right flank's clear.
I got nothing.
Left now!
And movin' fast!
Fastest Kaiju on record!
I don't see anything.
It's movin' too fast!
Eyes on the prize, gipsy.
600 meters from the drop.
400 meters and closing.
Bogeys are stopping.
Striker!
One o'clock.
Marshal, what are you doing?!
They're stopping.
Why the hell
are they stopping?!
I don't give a damn, sir!
We're 300 meters from the jump!
Something's not right!
Striker, the bogeys aren't following.
Take the leap now!
Don't do it! Don't do it,
it's not gonna work!
Move, you fascist!
Blowing up the breach,
it's not gonna work!
What do you mean?
What's not gonna work?
Sir, just because
the breach is open
Does not mean you're gonna be
able to get a bomb through.
The breach
genetically reads the Kaiju
Like a barcode at the supermarket
and then lets them pass.
Okay, so you're gonna have
to fool the breach
Into thinking that you have
the same code!
And how are we supposed
to do that?
By making it think
you are a Kaiju.
You have to lock onto the Kaiju,
ride it into the breach.
The throat will then read
The Kaiju's genetic code
and let you pass.
If you don't do it, the bomb
will deflect off the breach
Like it always has
and the mission will fail.
All right, now that
you've heard all that,
Striker, take the leap!
Sir! I have a third signature
emerging from the breach!
Third signature
emerging from the breach.
It's a triple event.
Oh, god, I was right.
How big is it?
What category?
Category 5.
Striker,
It's a category 5.
The first ever.
Striker, we see him.
We're right behind you,
about 100 meters.
We're gonna come around
your three o'clock,
Try to flank him.
Standard twoTeam
formation.
Just keep him busy
for a few mi..
Brace for impact!
Chain sword deployed.
Let's get this son of a bitch!
Gipsy, comin' up
on your 12 o'clock!
Full speed!
Get out of the way!
The release is jammed!
We can't deliver
the payload, sir!
We're still armed.
But the hull is compromised!
Half our systems
are offline, sir.
We need to override the..
Aah!
Both Kaijus converging
on striker fast!
Hang on, striker!
We're comin' to ya!
No! Gipsy!
Do not come to our aid!
Do you copy?
Hang on!
Stay as far back as you can!
We can still reach you.
We're comin' for you.
No, Raleigh, listen to me.
You know exactly
what you have to do!
Gipsy is nuclear!
Take her to the breach!
I hear you, sir.
Headin' for the breach.
Structural damage, 80%.
Now..
Mako. Listen.
You can finish this.
I'll always be here for you.
You can always find me
in the drift.
We're a walking
nuclear reactor.
We can destroy the breach.
What can we do, sir?
We can clear a path!
For the lady!
They're gonna detonate
the payload.
He said if you have the shot,
you take it!
So let's do this!
It was a pleasure, sir.
Sensei.
Aishitemasu.
All systems critical.
Fluid loss.
Systems are critical!
Fuel is leaking!
Our right leg's crippled!
Code red.
Let's finish this.
All systems critical.
What are they doing?
Finishing the mission.
Loccent.
We have the Kaiju carcass.
We're heading for the breach.
You guys better be right.
'Cause one way or another,
we're gettin' this thing done.
On my count, rear jets!
Three, two, one.
Now!
Hold on.
Mako's oxygen is down.
Half capacity!
Can you reroute it?
I'm tryin', sir.
Hold on, Mako.
Heat shaft purge.
I'm gonna burn
this son of a bitch.
They're in.
They're in!
It worked.
Oxygen main, left hemisphere,
critical levels.
Operating at 15% capacity.
10% capacity.
5% capacity.
He's givin' her his oxygen.
Right hemisphere oxygen..
It's okay now, Mako.
..Critical level.
We did it.
I can finish this alone.
All I have to do is fall.
Anyone can fall.
Raleigh, your oxygen
levels are critical now.
You don't have much time.
Start the core meltdown
and get out of there.
Do you hear me?
Get out of there now!
One pod is ejected.
No detonation, sir.
Loccent,
if you can still hear me,
I'm initiating
reactor override now.
Manual activation required.
What's goin' on?!
Trigger's offline!
He has to do it by hand.
He's out of time.
He has to
selfDestruct now.
Manual activation required.
No!
Manual override initiated.
Core meltdown in tMinus 60.
Reactor meltdown in 55 seconds.
50 seconds.
Evac pod engaged.
5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
Reactor meltdown commence.
Direct hit!
The breach has collapsed!
To the choppers!
To the choppers now!
Visuals on first pod.
Tracking solid.
Vital signs are good.
Okay, where's the second pod?
I'm tracking it, but I'm
getting no vital signs.
I can't find his pulse.
I don't think he's breathing.
Can you read his pulse?
Does he have a pulse?
Raleigh?
I don't know.
Mako, listen to me.
It could be the sensors
are not working.
We can't be sure.
No.
No. Don't go.
Mako.
Don't go. Please.
You're squeezing me too tight.
I couldn't breathe.
This is
marshal Hercules Hansen.
The breach is sealed.
Stop the clock!
Mako, Raleigh.
We have your position.
The choppers are on their way.
JJust hang on.
Are you okay?
Do you copy?
Uh, guys?
a  SELVAHEMA  presentation
^ When the earth collides
^ two hearts, two souls remain
^ one love of humankind
^ in heaven's name
^ no time for fear or blame
^ inside, we are the same
^ we feel it all
^ we feel the rise
before the fall ^
^ there's no dividing us
^ we feel it all
^ we feel it
^ the rise and fall
^ we drift inside each other
^ all we have is one another
^ united, we can never fall
^ we feel it all
^ we feel the rise
before the fall ^
^ there's no dividing us
^ we feel it all,
we feel it all ^
^ we feel it all
^ we feel the rise
before the fall ^
^ there's no dividing us
^ we feel it all,
we feel it all ^
^ great scientist minds
^ militaries combine to form
the greatest weapons ^
^ to defend mankind
^ from the bottomless pit
is the apocalypse ^
^ Egypt, Okinawa,
they threaten the populous ^
^ nations of man must stand
this terror ^
^ two hearts ripped apart,
they come together ^
^ some bonds we enjoin,
they cannot be severed ^
^ whether creed or color,
we all need each other ^
^ and look beyond these borders
to see each other ^
^ the fate of the world
is upon our shoulders ^
^ a soldier tells
his father goodbye ^
^ you see the crowd mist
^ a gleam of hope
appears in his eye ^
^ no one knows for whom
the bell tolls ^
^ a strong mighty body,
100 tons of steel ^
^ Kaiju
^ facing the enemy
that stands before us ^
^ we feel it all
^ they trying to destroy us
^ we feel the rise
before the fall ^
^ there's no dividing us
^ we feel it all,
we feel it all ^
^ we feel it all
^ we feel the rise
before the fall ^
^ there's no dividing us
^ we feel it all,
we feel it all ^
^ we drift inside each other
^ all we have is one another
^ united, we can never fall