My generation...
we were born into war.
Giant monsters attacked
our world.
We called 'em Kaiju.
They came through the Breach.
A gateway to another dimension
at the bottom
of the Pacific Ocean.
They were sent by an alien race
on the other side...
the Precursors.
We fought back,
building our own monsters.
Jaegars... giant robots.
So big they needed
two pilots to run 'em.
My father was one of them.
He sacrificed himself
to help save the world.
I... am not my father.
♪ Whoa ♪
♪ Ooh, yeah ♪
It's been ten years
since we won the war
and closed the Breach.
Most of the world's recovered.
But a few coastal cities
never did.
And the world is still
picking up the pieces.
♪ Wizzy boy, make me dance ♪
♪ Daddy Yo ♪
- ♪ Make me dance. ♪
- But some of us
live better in a broken world.
And squatting in half a mansion
is better than paying
for some crappy apartment.
Now, in the relief zones,
you have to get creative.
You have to hustle.
Or somebody else
might eat your breakfast.
And your cookies.
And your damn hot sauce.
You know, out here,
we place a different value
on things.
The Pan Pacific Defense Corps
usually looks the other way
as long as you don't go poking
around where you don't belong.
Say, like a...
decommissioned
Jaeger scrapyard.
Big risks mean big reward,
and nothing pays more
than stolen Jaeger tech.
Plenty of nutcases out here
trying to slap together
their own Jaegers.
But they need
the parts to do it.
So, if you can steal
what no one else can steal...
...you can live like a king.
Are you sure it's in here?
Power cores are stripped
before they get decommissioned.
But sometimes they miss
the tertiary plasma capacitors.
And that's a big score.
This one's still
holding a charge.
Oh.
You better hope so.
Okay.
Let's just calm down.
Let's not get excited.
I'm just playing the odds here.
You cheated Barada in Juarez,
skipped out on Chau
in Hong Kong.
Now, that was
a misunderstanding.
And stole from me...
in my own backyard.
Now I'm stealing for you.
Circle of life.
We good?
You deliver...
and yeah...
we're good.
Okay.
Let's get rich.
Let's.
Target lock.
Where is it?
Hey, man, uh,
just a little situation.
It says it's here.
It's supposed to be
right there,
but you know what,
let me just figure this out.
Target lock.
Somebody please kill this guy
for me.
Target moving.
No, no, no. It's here.
You wait, wait.
Someone else is in here.
Someone else has the capacitor.
Now, let's go. Come on.
Jake! Jake!
Hey, wait!
Son of a...
Go, go, go!
Split up.
Go!
Whoa!
Whoa! Whoa! Hey!
Come on! Jake!
Hey, boss, he went over here!
Go, go, go!
I see him. I see him.
This way.
Jake, Jake, Jake.
Nice try.
Yeah.
Jake!
- We're good.
- Jake!
Jake, you son of a...
Target lock.
Hey! Get back here with that!
No, no!
Target moving.
How old are you?
Old enough to kick your ass.
Ah-ah-ah-ah.
Let's take a second.
Back up.
You build this thing yourself?
What do you think?
I think I can sell
your little toy
- for a whole lot of money.
- Scrapper's not a toy
and she's not for sale.
The man holding the pipe
says she is.
So listen up...
You led them here?
That's impossible.
Hey!
Ah, what the hell, man?
Come on, come on, come on.
Yes.
It works!
Okay.
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Hey!
Get out.
What are you doing?
- No, no, no, no, no, no, no. Stop!
- Where is it?
Hey! Don't touch that. Hey.
What are you doing?!
- Stop!
- Where's the other one?
- The other what?
- The other cradle.
A Jaeger needs two pilots.
Scrapper is small enough to run
on a single neural lobe.
All right, then you get out,
you let me pilot.
Get out!
Screw that.
Told you she's not a toy.
You're gonna get us killed.
I can get us out of here.
I just got us out.
Oh, my God.
That's November Ajax.
Pilots of unregistered Jaeger,
this is the
Pan Pacific Defense Corps.
Power down
and exit your Conn-Pod.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Don't-don't-don't give up.
You give up way too easy.
That's what they think.
Stop!
You are in violation
of Code Ten,
Section 14.
Operation of
an unregistered Jaeger.
- Hang on.
- I am hanging on!
Hang tighter.
Seriously?
Stop.
See?
I just out-piloted
November Ajax.
No, you didn't.
Did.
Didn't.
Okay. What do you got?
And I'm not getting out.
- One of those ion cells redundant?
- No!
- They are now.
- But we need them.
- Get up to Ajax's head.
- What?
Go!
Power down.
Low power warning. 12%.
I told you we needed that!
It worked, didn't it?
11%.
How long before Ajax
can reboot his systems?
About that long.
Power down.
This is your final warning.
All right, let's go.
Look what you did to my Jaeger,
you jerk!
Should have let me pilot.
Oh, like this is my fault.
- You compromised my command center.
- Wow.
Your command center?
- Yes. My command center.
- Wait. Sorry, sorry.
- I didn't hear that. Your command center?
- Yes!
- Wait, that sorry excuse for a command...
- And you had no
place to come in
and try to tell me what to do.
I go where I want.
It's a different world, right?
'Cause it really worked out
well, right? Look where
- we're at, right?
- Your top lip and your bottom lip,
they need to meet
and become friends.
Smart. That's a good one.
Need to close up,
all right? Shut up.
- Shut up.
- Yeah, I can.
- Conversation done.
- Good.
Junkyard baby.
Why did you build it?
What happened
to the shutting up?
You said you wasn't
gonna sell it,
so what the hell
was you gonna do?
Rob a bank or something?
I built her because one day
they're gonna come back.
The Kaiju.
And when they do,
I'm not gonna be stuck waiting
for someone else
to come save my ass.
Not like before.
You. Let's go.
I don't really want to talk
about it. It's ridiculous.
That's just, like,
my right or...
Hello, Jake.
Here we are again.
It's just a stretch of
bad luck. I'll figure it out.
Father used to say
we make our own luck.
Yeah, well,
Dad said a lot of things.
You were arrested
in a rogue Jaeger.
Hold on a second.
That wasn't my Jaeger.
There's this little kid,
she's about this tall...
You have priors.
This is serious.
Okay.
That's why I need my big sis
to help me get the hell
out of here.
Just one last time.
They're not going
to let you just walk.
- But there might be another way.
- Okay.
See, that's what I want
to hear.
That's what I'm here
to talk about, the other way.
Lay it on me.
What do I got to do?
Reenlist and finish
what you started.
I'm not doing that.
I'm... look, I'm-I'm too old
to be a cadet.
I don't want you to be a cadet.
I want you to help train them.
Train who? Train what?
I'm not training no damn kids.
The transport is standing by
to bring both of you
to Moyulan.
Both of us?
You and your new recruit.
Mako.
I can't believe
she just hologrammed me.
Yeah, look,
I didn't have a choice.
I know, I get it, but why me?
Why do they want me
for the program?
You built and piloted
your own Jaeger.
These people like
that kind of stuff.
Okay, so then why
am I just a cadet
and you get to be a ranger?
Valor Omega.
Oh, my God.
That, that is Valor Omega.
Scrapper.
Hey!
You got to be kidding me.
I didn't believe it
when they told me
you were inbound.
How you doing, Nate?
It's Ranger Lambert.
Are you having a laugh?
Well, this is a military base.
You remember how that works,
Ranger Pentecost.
You must be Amara Namani.
Yes, sir.
Ranger, sir.
Well, let's get you
squared away.
Oh, and, uh,
try not to steal anything
while you're here.
Did that haircut
just call you Pentecost?
As in badass Stacker Pentecost?
Pilot of Coyote Tango, hero
of basically the whole world?
It's just a name.
Yeah, a really cool name.
Sim training starts at 0600.
You're late, you miss the day.
You fall behind,
you'll be on the next transport
back to wherever
they found you.
That's Titan Redeemer.
And Bracer Phoenix.
She's a three-man rig.
Saber Athena.
I love Saber Athena.
She's the fastest Jaeger
in the fleet.
Did you know that?
Warning: stand clear of lift.
Okay, so which one's yours?
Gipsy.
- You pilot Gipsy Avenger?
- He used to
until his copilot got a better
offer in the private sector.
Jules Reyes, J-Tech.
Amara, cadet.
Jake.
Ranger, apparently.
Heard a lot about you,
Pentecost.
Yeah?
You know you still hold
the record?
- What record?
- Shut up.
So how did they lure you back?
I mean, it couldn't have been
the pay, so...
Oh, yeah, it's a long story,
but if you,
if you want to talk about it,
we can meet up...
She's busy.
Ranger.
Eyes front, Pentecost.
Oh! Come on, Renata,
not the face!
- Sorry, man. Ooh!
- Oh!
Ah!
And raise you two shower chits.
Fold, Ilya.
You need all the showers
you can get, man.
I have a musk!
What you smell is musk.
Ranger on deck!
Audio system deactivated.
Cadets.
This is Amara Namani.
She'll be joining you in
sim training bright and early.
And this is Ranger Pentecost.
He will be helping me
instruct you
until I can find a new copilot
to replace Ranger Burke.
Anything you'd like to add?
Nothing you want to hear.
Malikova, get Namani squared
away and prepped for training.
Yes, sir!
As you were.
Pentecost.
We're gonna be trained
by a Pentecost!
So? Not like he was the one who
died helping close the Breach.
He's never even been in combat.
Renata, let's go for round two.
Yo, Ilya, you see this? Ah!
Uh, hey.
So, where should I...?
Heard you built
your own little Jaeger.
Yeah, actually.
Uh, Scrapper.
I operated her, too,
with this solo bay...
You want to put junk together,
be a mechanic.
Moyulan is for pilots.
Hey, come on. I got ya.
- Thanks.
- Yeah.
- Um...
- Jinhai.
Ou-yang Jinhai.
So, you and Vik
already buddies, huh?
- Vik?
- It's short for Viktoriya.
But you don't want
to call her that.
Yeah, what's her problem?
- Took her three shots to pass the entrance test.
- Yeah.
Don't think she likes
how you landed here.
Yeah, well, it's not my fault.
Recruiters never
come around back home.
- Hey, know any Russian?
- No.
I'll teach you some.
Calms her down.
Come on.
Let's get you squared away.
Aah!
Hemispheres out of alignment.
- Warning.
- We need to reconnect!
I know! I'm trying!
MAGLEV deactivated.
I just can't get this.
That sucked.
Drift simulation terminated.
You know, when I heard
you gave November Ajax
a run for his money,
I thought we might have
something here.
Now I'm not so sure.
How am I supposed to drift
in this thing?
It smells like feet.
I didn't ask for
your excuses, Cadet.
You putting her
up against Kaiju
that almost killed veteran
pilots doesn't make any sense.
Well, maybe she's not the only
one that doesn't belong here.
Wow. See, Nate, I know
you have a problem with me.
But come on.
She's just a kid.
So were we.
That's the point.
You make stronger connections
when you're young.
And that kind of bond makes
for a better drift pilot.
Yeah. I remember the pitch.
Thanks.
Ryoichi, Renata, you're up.
Show our new recruit
how it's done.
♪ I just wanna be
a better man ♪
- Oh.
- ♪ To my baby ♪
♪ Mm, mm... ♪
What the hell are you wearing?
Jules loves it.
Yeah, she told me
it's nice to finally have
someone with style around here.
Can't blame the girl.
- I'm sexy.
- Mm. Yeah.
- Want a drink?
- Sure.
Thanks.
Ice cream's up top.
Yes. Yes.
So, one more time around, huh?
Prove your old man wrong?
Nah, I just came back to see
if your chin implant
ever settled in.
- Well, I think it's settled in quite nicely.
- Yeah.
It's very commanding.
Kids must love it.
Jake, these kids,
they look up to us.
Mm-hmm.
We got to show them
that we can work together.
Well, the war ended
ten years ago, man.
You just need to let that go.
Just... woosah.
Y-You have to understand
your enemy's ob...
You have...
Sorry, mate.
You have to understand
your enemy's objective
to know you've defeated 'em.
- We still don't.
- No.
I can help you out with that.
See, I'm thinking it has
something to do with them
sending giant monsters
to kick the crap out of us.
No, no, no.
The Precursors wouldn't send
Kaiju to flatten a few cities
if they were trying
to wipe us all out.
All right, look, Nate, I don't
have a problem with you, man.
But I had to make a choice.
It was between
your pretty face and prison.
I chose your pretty face.
Oh, well, I'm touched.
And how many damn toppings
do you need?
Leave my toppings be, man.
Don't mess with
my damn toppings.
So the cadets got, like, what,
couple of months
before they graduate?
- Six.
- Okay. I'll tell you what.
Every time you want to say
something soldiery to 'em,
I'll just nod, or like,
"Yep, what he said."
And then, before you know it,
they get to be pilots.
- And I get to get back to my life.
- Great.
Boom.
It may happen
sooner than you think.
How so?
Big dog and pony show tomorrow.
Shao and her team
are presenting
this new drone program
they have.
Could make us all obsolete.
Sounds like my
"get out of jail free" card.
You know, you can front
all you want,
but you and I both know
you could've been great.
Ms. Shao, Marshall Quan.
It's an honor to meet you.
Sorry.
She doesn't do
the whole hand shaking thing.
Dr. Newton Geiszler,
head of research
and development
for Shao Industries.
That's a nice firm,
firm grip you got there, uh...
Hand hard very shake.
Thank you for having us.
Ranger Lambert and I will
get you set up, ma'am.
That's a much better
look on you.
Guess it's better than
prison stripes. Barely.
I-I'm sorry, is this him?
It-It's got to be him, right?
You're Stacker's kid.
Hey, uh, I'm Newt.
I was, uh, I was a big fan
of your father's.
Amazing speech writer,
by the way.
Did you ever hear his one where
he canceled the apocalypse?
- Newton.
- Hermann.
I was hoping you'd be
tagging along.
I could use your help on
an experiment I'm working on.
Now, this will
only take a moment.
- I know how busy you are.
- Yeah.
Don't want to impose,
but, uh...
Aw, come on,
you can't impose on me.
I mean, we've been inside
each other's heads, right?
We've saved the world.
We've drifted with a Kaiju!
You know, if we hadn't
yanked that intel
out of that Kaiju's brain,
Raleigh would've never
been able to close the Breach.
Now, that was you
and that was me.
Technically more me,
but any chance we could
make this quick or...?
- Um, deployment.
- Huh?
Of Jaegers.
Deploying them into battle,
it takes, takes too much time.
The amount of damage
a Kaiju can inflict
before they've ev...
Ah, here.
I think I've found a solution.
Hermann, you know I can
never read your, uh...
Uh, rocket thrusters, huh?
Yeah. No.
No. There's no fuel
in the world
with that kind of
boost-to-mass ratio.
From this world.
No.
I-Is that Kaiju blood?
Exactly.
I've discovered Kaiju blood
is highly reactive
when it's combined
with rare earth elements...
cerium, lanthanum, gadolinium.
I realize that, pal. Okay.
Y-You can't be fooling around
with this stuff.
You're gonna blow yourself up.
Uh...
Now, no one knows more about
Kaiju morphology than you.
- Okay.
- And if you could just take a look, please.
No, Hermann, I got to stop you.
Look, none of this matters.
Once my boss' drones
are approved,
deployment time,
that's gonna be a non-issue.
Within a year, buddy, we're
gonna have drones everywhere.
So you won't help me?
Look, why don't we talk about
it over dinner at my place?
Okay? You can
finally meet Alice.
I don't need
a hot meal, Newton.
What I need is a solution
to a very specific problem.
Hey.
Ah, that's me, bud.
I'm sorry. Duty calls.
It's been nice catching up.
Newton.
I, um...
I still get nightmares
about what we saw
when we drifted with
that disgusting Kaiju brain.
Yeah.
But... it was a hell
of a rush, wasn't it?
Dr. Geizler, time to go.
Okay, okay.
You and Dr. Gottleib
were close, weren't you?
During the war?
Oh, uh...
We shared lab yes okay-
Speak English, your Mandarin
makes you sound like an idiot.
I-I know, I'm terrible.
Uh, yes, we shared
a lab together.
What were you and Dr.
Gottlieb talking about?
Oh, some crazy idea
he had about
thruster pods
on a, on a Jaeger.
Until Secretary General Mori makes her
recommendation at the council summit,
I can't afford a misstep.
No more contact with him...
until after the vote.
Oh. Well, the man's
completely harmless. Uh...
Uh, okay.
Could you say that again,
and this time about 80% slower?
I said don't make me question
your loyalty. Understand?
Ay.
What's to question?
I... look, I barely
talk to the guy anyway.
Then it won't be a problem.
And work on your Mandarin,
I do not like to repeat
myself.
In any language.
My drones are the next step
in Jaeger evolution.
The system I designed
processes commands
through a quantum data core.
This means that a single pilot
can operate the drone remotely
from anywhere in the world.
As soon as the council
approves deployment,
based on Secretary General
Mori's final report,
the days of struggling
to find and train
drift compatible pilots
will be a thing of the past.
And you think a bunch of desk
jockeys are better than us?
We are not here
to shut you down.
Cooperation between
our programs
has never been more vital.
If there are any questions.
Yeah, I got a question right over here!
We are pilots,
not a bunch of office workers!
And now we're shouting.
There's no need to shout.
Well, that was slick.
So, how long until all this is
shut down so I can go home?
I don't trust the tech.
Not yet, at least.
Well, it looks
pretty good to me.
Remote systems can be
hacked or compromised.
No, you've got
the key vote, right?
So there you go.
It's your decision.
I wish I could just
go ahead and approve them.
Nearly half the council
is backing Liwen.
They aren't going to like
my decision.
Who cares what they like
and what they don't like?
I'll tell you what,
I'm gonna go with you.
For moral support.
Plus, I want to get
out of this place.
I'm glad you offered,
because I already requested
Gipsy Avenger as honor guard
at the Council Summit.
Look, you know
Gipsy's Nate's ride.
His copilot works for
Liwen now. He needs a new one.
One that you already know
is drift compatible.
All right.
I'll do it.
I got your back.
But I want to be there
when you tell Nate,
'cause I just want
to see his face.
He's gonna be so pissed.
He's just gonna
stand there like,
"Yeah, I don't think
you belong in a Jaeger, Jake.
Get out of my Jaeger.
I'm handsome and sexy."
He is handsome.
He is sexy.
Thank you, Jake.
Welcome back. Lots of sunshine
today to kick off our weekend.
The city...
Good afternoon, everyone.
Peter Overton broadcasting
from the Nine Studios
in Sydney with the latest...
So far, police say
at least 49 officers injured.
Kaiju
worshippers in black masks
throwing bottles and rocks.
PPDC security in riot gear
are attempting
to regain control...
Gipsy Avenger,
this is Marshal Quan.
All you have to do is stand
there and look pretty.
Stay focused,
try not to fall over.
Roger that, sir.
Go for drop.
In three, two, one.
Drop!
Jake!
Drift alignment unstable.
Relax.
It's coming back to me.
- You sure?
- Ion cells activated.
And hey... We're in each
other's heads, remember?
So I'd appreciate it if you'd
stop thinking about Jules.
Not gonna happen.
How about you stop thinking
about kicking my ass?
Not gonna happen either.
Gonna be a long day.
Hemispheres are calibrated, sir.
Neural handshake is weak,
but holding.
Incoming transport.
- Warning.
- Gipsy to Command.
You reading this?
Gipsy, this is Command.
Be advised,
we have a rogue Jaeger.
Pilots of unregistered Jaeger,
power down and exit
your Conn-Pod immediately.
I repeat:
power down and exit
your Conn-Pods now.
Missiles fired!
Low power.
- Warning.
- We're losing power!
Jake! That Jaeger's
power reading is the same...
It's jamming our comms!
- Nate!
- Power's up!
Ah!
Oh, shit.
- What do we do?
- Follow my lead!
Mako's hit!
She's going down!
We've gotta move!
Activating gravity sling!
Mayday! Mayday! Mayday!
This is Mike, Mike, Charlie,
zero, five, two!
We have been hit
and we are going down!
- And we are going down!
- Sending.
- Mako!
- Jake!
Wait!
Drift alignment failing.
Come on, Sarah!
- Do something...
- Drift alignment failing.
...you stupid brain thing!
- Hey.
So, I'm not really good
at emotional stuff, but...
I really am sorry
about your sister.
Half sister? I...
Yeah, her family died
during the Onibaba attack.
My dad took her in.
And she was my sister.
My family.
Why are you out of uniform?
Just had a lot on my mind
after Sydney.
Guess I just wanted
to be comfortable.
Well, don't let Ranger Lambert
see you in that.
He might take the stick out of
his butt and beat you with it.
I think I'm safe.
It's wedged in there
pretty tight.
So they're still using Sarah.
Yeah.
And I can't drift with her
for some reason.
All the other cadets
have been training for years
and I just...
I hate feeling
like the slow kid.
You gotta relax.
Or you're just grinding gears.
- I'll help you out.
- Got it, coach.
- Don't call me coach.
- All right, sensei.
Concentrate.
You have to make
a good connection.
You can't do that
if you're yappin' your gums.
You ready?
Ready.
All right.
Let's see if
we're drift compatible.
Get him!
Shoot! Come on!
Neural load exceeding limit.
Stay focused, Amara.
Remember,
the stronger your connection,
the better you fight.
That's it.
Amara! Come on, jump!
Jump to me, baby!
You have to, Amara, come on!
- Jump!
- Amara!
Don't hang on to the memory.
Just let it flow
right through you.
Amara!
Amara! Jump in there!
Yeah, come on.
Get together. Ready?
One, two, cheese!
Got it.
Want to see?
Wait a sec.
Amara.
Amara, you need to let it go.
Amara!
Look, just listen to my voice!
- Amara!
- Daddy!
Daddy!
Amara! Come on, jump!
Amara!
We need to break the drift!
Jump to me! Come on!
I'm scared!
Baby, I will catch you,
I promise. Come on!
- Amara!
- Amara, come on!
Jump!
Amara!
Take it off!
Hey.
Are you okay?
I was there.
I felt it.
Yeah.
I felt it, too.
Jake, it's me.
You there?
Yeah, I'm here.
Meet me in the lab right away.
Marshal wants to see us.
All right.
I'm on my way.
You okay?
- What is it?
- A message. From Mako.
She was trying
to send it from her copter
right before it went down.
It's a data package.
High density.
Obsidian Fury
was jamming comms.
How could her signal
get through?
It didn't.
- At least not intact.
- So it's gone?
Well, "gone" is
relative in the digital realm.
By running a modified
fractal algorithm,
I might be able to reconstruct
a few megabytes.
There.
Is that a Kaiju?
I'm checking against
PPDC Kaiju archives.
No match against the database.
Keep looking.
Whatever this is,
it was important to her.
I want to know why.
And I want to know who was
piloting that rogue Jaeger.
Hey.
Sorry I'm, uh, I-I'm late.
I-I thought you were
still in Sydney.
The council has approved Drone deployment
in an emergency session.
Oh.
Uh...
that's great.
Thought you'd be a little
more enthusiastic, Doc.
Yeah, no, I'm-I'm pumped.
This is great.
Uh, it's just
the timing of everything,
with the attack and all,
- feels a little...
- I was there.
I know what happened.
And it wouldn't have...
if our Drones had been in the field.
Neural connection terminated.
Now everyone sees that.
Yeah.
Uh, I guess they do.
Which means the attack was positive...
all things considered.
If you look at it sideways
and you squint,
then maybe you could say that.
Uh, I'm sorry, what are you...
what... what's going on here?
The council expects full deployment
within 48 hours.
48 is a...
I've worked my whole life for this.
Get it done.
Okay.
Yeah.
Not a problem.
That-That'll be fine.
48 hours? No way we'll be ready.
Y-You don't think
there's a way?
All right, well,
then you're fired.
Okay? How about that?
Or maybe you're promoted.
I don't know.
We'll see how it goes.
Just get it done!
Give me this.
Hey, honey!
I'm home!
Sorry I'm late.
God, things were...
things were crazy today,
with what happened in Sydney.
♪ This
mountain I must climb... ♪
All those people...
it was, uh, not pretty.
My boss almost got killed.
That could've been bad.
Maybe.
I guess, I don't know.
That would've been great,
actually,
that one is all over me.
I mean, I can't get
a break from her!
I'm ranting.
Enough about work.
And enough about her, really,
I should be focused on you.
How about we have
a little fun in the bedroom?
How was your day?
Oh. That's great.
Yeah, that's, uh,
that's exciting.
What's that?
A little pick-me-up?
Well...
...what can I say?
You read my mind.
♪ I want to know what love is ♪
♪ Oh, oh ♪
♪ I want you to show me. ♪
Hundreds of police officers...
They're calling it
Obsidian Fury.
There's never been a rogue
like this.
News feed said
they were posting a dozen
Jaegers at the memorial.
When I die, I want that many
to send me off.
Your pop's gonna make you work
with boobs when you wash out.
Jaegers do not show up
when the boob guy dies.
Wait, your dad
works with boobs?
He's a plastic surgeon.
He doesn't just work with...
I'm not gonna wash out.
I'm gonna be a pilot.
Still. You die,
meh, I post one Jaeger
at your funeral.
Maybe half a Jaeger.
I heard that's where
they found Amara.
In half a Jaeger.
It was a whole Jaeger.
It just wasn't very big,
Viktoriya.
Bigger is better.
What did you say?
Am I saying that right?
Yep.
- Ah!
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa!
- Guys.
I worked every day of my life
to be here.
You didn't do anything.
You were just picked up
off the street like garbage!
Guys, come on!
Hey, hey.
- Hey! Whoa, whoa, whoa!
- You know where I learned that?
On the streets,
you big, dumb...
Ranger on deck!
She jumped me!
She doesn't belong here!
I don't care!
You know, when I first joined
the Corps, I was just like you.
Worse. I was nobody.
But that woman
we laid to rest today,
Mako Mori, she said,
"Whoever you are,
"the minute you enter this
program, you join a family.
"And no matter what they do,
no matter how stupid
they may act sometimes..."
"...you forgive 'em
and you move on."
So you start believing that.
In here.
And you'll start believing
in a Jaeger.
Hey.
Marshal's looking for you guys.
Says Gottlieb found something.
It isn't something.
It's somewhere.
Severnaya Zemlya.
Off Siberia's Taymyr Peninsula.
What's in Zemlya?
Well, nothing anymore.
A facility roughly
in this location
was used to manufacture Jaeger
power cores earlier in the war.
- But it was decommissioned years ago.
- Why would
Mako be trying to tell us
about an abandoned factory
in the middle of nowhere?
Sir, permission
to take Gipsy Avenger
to see what the hell's
out there.
Scanning.
Looks like
Mako's message was a dead end.
This place is abandoned.
No, no, wait a second.
I'm getting
some weird readings.
Incoming!
Take out his legs!
We got to get out of here!
Plasma cannon!
- Think we pissed him off.
- Good.
You remember our old move?
Hell yeah.
He looks hurt!
Go for his power core!
Ah!
Warning.
Pilots of Obsidian Fury,
get the hell out
of your Conn-Pod!
What the hell is that?
It's definitely Kaiju.
A secondary brain used to
control the hindquarters.
How'd they get into our world?
There hasn't been a breach
in ten years.
Sensors would've picked it up.
I don't think
there was a breach.
Kaiju flesh...
has a distinct radioactive
half-life signature.
Particular to the Anteverse.
This specimen does not.
Wait, so, you're-you're saying
that it's from our universe?
The genetic fingerprints
indicate distinctly terrestrial
modification techniques,
probably engineered
from Kaiju flesh left over
from the war.
Precursors didn't do this.
Humans did.
Oh, my God.
That hunk of slimy crap
was piloting Obsidian Fury?
We got to get a look inside.
Inside?
That thing's part Kaiju.
Come on, guys. When are we
ever gonna get a chance
to see something
like this again?
Never.
Never would be good.
You guys can stay here.
I'm going.
No, Amar... Amara.
Guys, guys,
we should not be in here.
Whoa.
It's fused all the way
through the system.
Like... muscle tissue.
That's how it was able
to move like it did.
- Cool.
- Yeah, cool.
Working with boobs is sounding
better and better.
Shine your light over here.
Oh, yeah, let's just
go yank on the guts
of the weird-ass Kaiju killbot.
What is it?
I think it's some sort of...
Jinhai!
I told you
not to yank on those.
Go get help! Go!
Man, we are so screwed!
This goes way past
what she did.
The decision has been made.
Security will take it
from here.
We're done!
Is Jinhai okay?
He's got some scarring,
but yeah, he'll live.
Marshal put him on probation.
Meilin and Suresh, too.
They blink wrong,
all of 'em are out.
No, it's not their fault.
- I talked them into it.
- I'm sorry, I tried to talk
to the marshal, but...
you're dismissed
from the program.
Never belonged here anyway.
Really?
You know, I used to say
the same thing a long time ago.
But I actually didn't
want to be here.
Still don't.
Why'd you sign up?
We were at war.
And my dad
was leading the charge
and I thought...
maybe I could see more of him.
Maybe even drift with him.
Well, one night,
me and Nate got into it.
It was over something stupid.
I can't even remember what.
So I climbed in an old Mark 4
just to show him I didn't
need him to be a great pilot.
That's pretty dumb.
- Yeah.
- How far'd you get?
- About seven steps, well, take or leave.
- How far did you get?
About two steps, then
I blacked out from the strain.
And the first thing I saw
when I woke up was my dad,
just standing right
in front of me, looking stern.
Wh-What'd he say?
He said I was
out of the program.
He said I didn't deserve
to be in a Jaeger.
Look, he said a lot of things.
A year later, my dad was gone.
And I didn't get a chance
to prove him wrong.
More importantly, I didn't get
a chance to prove it to myself.
You listen to me.
Don't let what other people
think of you
define who you are.
You won't like
where that takes you.
Do you understand?
And keep your head up.
And you might just be
as good-looking as me
in this type of situation.
Seriously.
This face is, is set up well.
Beauty is a burden.
You'll be all right.
Shao Industries.
What?
Obsidian Fury has tech in it
made by Shao Industries.
That's impossible.
Jules and her team
scanned every centimeter
of that Jaeger.
Insulating metamaterials
wound counterclockwise
in the shunt cabling.
Shao's the only company
that winds them that way.
Amara, are you sure about what
you're telling me right now?
Yes.
Yeah.
I stole a ton to make Scrapper.
I thought
it might be important.
Yeah.
Thank you.
Shao Industries?
They don't even have
a bio division.
Yeah, not that we know of.
Cabling could have been stolen,
just like in Amara's Jaeger.
We're gonna need more than that
to connect Fury to Shao.
What about Newt?
He'd have access
to the internal records,
- the shipping manifests...
- All right.
Go see him.
Keep a low profile.
I have a mission?
Finally.
We'll take what we know
to the marshal.
The building is secure, ma'am.
No visitors without the proper credentials.
I don't want anyone interfering
with deployment.
What is it?
I'll be in my office.
Okay.
This isn't fair.
I'm sorry.
You don't deserve this.
It was my fault.
This is on me.
Amara.
The next Jaeger you build...
make it a big one.
System online.
And we have delivery
at 100%, people.
- System online.
- A hundred percent!
That's the way
that it's done, okay?
I told you we could do it, and we did it!
Malfunction.
I'm losing uplink to drone 375!
- Why?
- Malfunction.
Why? Figure out why!
We'll take what we know
to the council in person.
Prep a transport.
Give me a second.
The Drones in the field are malfunctioning!
Stop the ones coming in from deploying!
Get to Gipsy! Go!
All pilots,
man your Jaegers
and engage hostiles!
Okay, you got this.
You cool?
Yeah, super cool.
Just, uh, just stay calm.
Doctor Geiszler! Shao's looking for you?
I-I know. I'm heading up!
I'm heading right...
Hermann.
Uh, what are you doing here?
How'd you get in here?
I do have PPDC credentials,
and besides,
everyone else seems
a little bit preoccupied
with the killer drones
your boss just set off!
- She used you.
- No.
- She lured you with money and a fancy title.
- No. No way.
And while you were
basking in the glow,
she took your research
and she twisted it.
Help me stop her, Newton.
Help me save the world
like old times.
All right, technically, uh,
you were helping me last time.
- Let's get that straight.
- Fine.
Help me help you
save the world.
What do you say?
Well, I say, um, I say...
Don't shoot!
Uh...
Goddamn it!
Why can't I get this language?
- What's happening?!
- Amara! Are those Jaegers?
No, they're drones
from Shao Industries.
What are they doing?
I don't know.
They just went crazy.
Hey! Clear the deck now!
Get back to your quarters
right now!
- Yes, sir! Go, go, go!
- Go! Go!
Go! Get the hell out of here!
Come on!
Come on.
Come on, come on.
Get up.
Really? Now?
Hermann! A little help!
Next time, why don't you learn
how to use a gun!
Take that!
Vile, vile individual!
- Thank you, Newton.
- Yeah.
I'd hug you if I didn't
have a rule about
- public displays of affection.
- It's fine.
- Oh, to hell with it.
- Okay. All right.
If you're done groping me,
let's take care
of the drones, right?
- Mm.
- Okay.
Shut down all systems! Now!
Everyone, get out of the lab
or I will shoot you!
I will shoot you twice!
- Always knew you'd go nuts!
- You're officially fired. Get out.
What do we do?
How do we stop this?
- There's a back door, Hermann.
- To what?
To the drone subroutine.
I added a subroutine just
in case I want to get in here
- and poke around down the road.
- Oh, sneaky bastard.
I know, right?
What did you just do?
What I've been planning
the last ten years.
I'm ending the world.
Where the hell are my pilots?!
Sitrep!
Breaches detected, multiple locations!
It's the Drones, sir!
All pilots, breaches detected.
Drones in the field
are opening multiple breaches
across the Pacific Rim.
Why?
Why would you do this?
Why would I do this? Mm.
Well, I guess I wouldn't.
Well, not normally,
not really my style.
Yeah, no, I don't know, maybe
I hate you all for treating me
like an insignificant
little joke of a man.
Maybe that's why he did it,
Hermann... I did it.
Uh, see.
There you go.
There's the problem.
I'm just not feeling
totally myself these days.
You.
Precursors.
Very good, Hermann,
you figured it out.
And as usual, a step behind.
Newton. You are a good man.
- No. Uh, Hermann.
- You must stop.
No, there's no point
in fighting them.
- You must fight back.
- I'm not strong enough, Hermann.
- Please, Newton. You must!
- I am not strong enough.
He is not strong enough!
None of you are strong enough!
I'm sorry, Hermann.
They're in my head.
Let him go!
You're not going to ruin my life's work.
Oh, hey, boss.
Go, go, go, go,
go, go, go, go, go!
What the hell
are you doing here?
- I told you to get to quarters!
- All the doors are blocked!
What do we do?!
How did you do it without me knowing?
I mean, 38% of your company
is fully automated.
It really wasn't very hard to
reallocate a little over here
and a little over there,
and slip in a little Kaiju
surprise without you noticing.
Especially since you always thought...
you were the smartest person in the room.
In about a second, I'm going to be.
Stop! Wait, wait, wait!
Newt's not in control
of himself!
It isn't him!
It's the Precursors.
They must have infected
his mind
when we drifted with the Kaiju.
Shut up!
Security, find and detain Dr. Geiszler.
If he tries to resist,
put a bullet in his head.
You stay here. We're gonna
try and get to Gipsy.
You ready for this?
- No. You?
- No.
- On three.
- Great.
One, two...
Hello? Anyone there?
Gottlieb?
Jake! Thank God.
We're under attack!
You need to force Liwen
- to shut down the drones!
- It isn't her.
It isn't Liwen.
It-it was Newt.
The Precursors,
they've infected him.
They're controlling his mind.
Gottlieb, can you get him
to disable the drones?
No. He got away.
Gottlieb, shut 'em down.
I've penetrated the subroutine.
It-It's trying to lock you out.
Feedback loop.
Gottlieb,
what the hell is going on?
Gottlieb!
Gottlieb, shut 'em down
or we're gonna die!
Shut 'em down!
Yes!
Liwen has disabled the drones.
The breaches are closed.
I repeat,
the breaches are closed.
Oh, no.
"Oh, no" what?
Three Kaiju
have gotten through.
South Korea, Russian coast,
and East China Sea.
Two Cat 4s and a Cat 5.
Copy that.
Get back to the dome.
We're gonna need
all the help we can get.
You girls okay?
- Yes, ma'am!
All right, what do we got?
The reports are
still coming in,
but drones took out Jaegers and
Shatterdomes across the Rim.
All right. How many Jaegers
do we have here?
Operational?
Gipsy Avenger, barely.
- That's it? - Yeah.
- Okay. We need more Jaegers
up and running or this is
gonna be a short fight.
Even if we can,
all of our other pilots
are either dead
or severely injured.
Okay, okay,
one disaster at a time.
Let's just focus
on those Jaegers.
Smallie, come over here.
I need you to help Jules
with the repairs.
- Can you do that?
- I thought I was kicked out.
I'm kicking you back in.
She's pretty good
at turning junk into Jaegers.
You good with that?
- Hell yeah.
- Right, we got a lot of work to do
and not a lot of time.
We got incoming!
I brought some help!
Hakuja, Shrikethorn,
and the big fella, Raijin.
I took the liberty of
assigning the designations.
Well, the spiky guy
and the big idiot
are moving away from the cities
and towards the ocean.
- What does that mean?
- Maybe they're trying
to link up with Hakuja
in the East China Sea.
Yeah, I bet Newt would know
what they're up to,
if we can get it out of him.
Yeah, we'd have
to find him first.
Any Jaegers closer
to those Kaiju than us?
What was left of the Chin-do
and the Sakhalinsk domes
tried to intercept...
emphasis on "tried."
I'm afraid we're on our own.
There's got to be
something here.
Something in
the East China Sea.
Maybe that's not
where they're headed.
Pull up a map of
Kaiju movement from the war.
Pushing data to main display.
What, do you know
something we don't?
You said we need to understand
our enemy's objective
to know we've beaten them.
What if the Kaiju
weren't blindly attacking
our cities during the war?
What if we were
just in their way?
Well, right here.
Mount Fuji, Japan.
Extrapolate for Hakuja,
Shrikethorn and Raijin.
Mount Fuji? But why?
- Rare earth elements.
- Huh?
Mount Fuji is a volcano
rich in rare earth elements.
Kaiju blood reacts
extremely violently
with rare earth elements
is the basis of
my fuel-thruster experiments.
Excuse me.
Oh, that sounds bad.
That's bad, right?
Very. Mount Fuji's active,
a geological pressure point.
Based on the blood-to-mass
ratio of the Kaiju,
the reaction would cause
a cascade event,
igniting the Ring of Fire
around the Pacific Rim.
Billions of tons
of toxic gas and ash
will spew into the atmosphere,
wiping out all life.
And finish terraforming
the Earth for the Precursors.
We can't let 'em
reach Mount Fuji.
I'm gonna check with Jules
for Jaeger repairs.
Even if we had
a hundred Jaegers,
there's no way
to intercept in time.
- What about your thruster pods?
- Oh, no, no, no, no.
They're not, they're not ready.
- Can they be?
- Well, in theory,
if it, um...
maybe, with-with your help.
Gottlieb, what does that mean,
"in theory"?
Today...
it means yes!
Power partially
restored in sectors two...
Saber Athena, Guardian Bravo,
and Bracer Phoenix
are good to go.
It's not a lot to work with.
If Liwen can patch
some Fury tech into Gipsy,
that might help.
Okay.
- Prep everything we got for deployment.
- Okay.
Don't get yourself killed.
You either.
Well, that's confusing.
Let's just stay focused.
We got four Jaegers against
two Category 4s and a Fiver.
It's better than just Gipsy.
We still need pilots.
We have 'em.
Oh, shit.
If my dad was here, he'd
probably give you a big speech.
Make you feel invincible.
I'm not my father.
I'm not a hero like he was.
Like Raleigh Becket
and Mako Mori.
But they didn't start out
that way.
They started out as cadets,
just like you.
We remember them as giants
because they stood tall.
Because they stood together.
It doesn't matter
who your parents are,
where you came from,
who believed in you
and who didn't.
We are a family now.
And we are Earth's
last defense.
This is our time, this is our
chance to make a difference.
Now let's mount up
and get it done!
Do you understand?
Yes, sir!
Jaeger pilots,
do you understand?!
Yes, sir!
- Do you understand?!
- Yes, sir!
Now help me save the world.
Let's do this.
- System online.
- Initiating neural handshake.
Establishing neural link.
Amara, jump in there!
- Neural handshake strong and steady.
- So...
how does it feel
to be in a real Jaeger?
- Bigger's not bad.
- All right,
all Jaegers sound off.
Go-no-go for launch.
Guardian Bravo, go.
Saber Athena, go.
Bracer Phoenix,
let's go already.
Copy that.
Command, we are go for launch.
Roger, Gipsy Avenger.
Ignition in ten seconds.
Nine,
eight,
seven, six,
five, four,
three, two,
one.
Ignition!
Warning.
Exceeding structural limits.
♪ Tro-lo-lo-lo-lo,
lo-lo-lo, lo-lo-lo... ♪
What the hell?
My grandmother used
to play it for me.
- Keeps me calm.
- What about me?
Not calm, man, not calm.
♪ Lo-lo-lo-lo-lo-lo,
lo-lo-lo-lo-lo-lo, lo ♪
♪ Oh... ♪
I knew it would work.
Gipsy to Command.
Targets acquired.
Roger that, Gipsy.
Everyone in the city is secured
in underground shelters.
You are clear to engage.
Solid copy. Going hot.
Bracer Phoenix, on me.
We'll take Raijin.
Roger that, Gipsy.
Saber Athena, Guardian Bravo,
- you take the other two.
- Copy that.
It's our turn
to save the world.
- Let's hope so.
- On my mark.
Three, two,
one, mark!
Fire!
Gipsy, Raijin's faceplates
are absorbing the hits
and throwing the energy
back at you!
Let's see it absorb this.
How many buildings
can this thing take?!
Shrikethorn inbound!
Hey, guys, we could use
a little help over here!
- Right now!
- Copy that, Saber.
Vik, take out Shrikethorn.
On it.
Saber Athena, Guardian Bravo
coming to assist!
Activating arc whip!
Yeah, that's right!
You better run!
These things ain't that tough.
Bracer Phoenix, watch your six!
Hostile inbound!
Copy that!
Yeah!
Whoo!
Okay, we're going
with giant robots again.
All right, real original, guys.
I'm not impressed.
I am not impressed.
We've got movement!
Multiple hostiles,
three kilometers southeast.
Liwen!
Are you reading this?
That's one of my automated
factories.
It was Newt.
He's in Tokyo.
Locating his position.
Hostiles, one klick away
and closing fast!
All Jaegers, brace for contact.
Disengage and brace
for contact!
All right.
Let's go, all right.
Go, go, go, go!
Go, baby, go, baby!
Where they going?
Well, he's pretty big.
All Jaegers, advance
and fire everything you've got
on my command!
Go!
Guardian, stand down!
We've got this!
Negative!
That's an order!
You freaking teenagers.
Go for the eyes!
- Which ones?
- All of them.
Ilya, Suresh, report.
Do you copy?
Come on, guys, sound off!
Guardian Bravo,
give me a sitrep.
You guys okay?
Guardian's down.
I'm pinned in the Conn-Pod.
Suresh.
Suresh didn't make it, sir.
Copy, Guardian.
You just stay put,
and we'll send you help
as soon as we can.
Bracer Phoenix, report.
You guys okay?
We're a little banged up,
but we're still in the fight.
Us, too, Saber.
I mean, Saber Athena, sir!
Saber, Bracer,
prepare to intercept
at the following coordinates.
- Let's finish this.
- Move your ass,
- and don't be late.
- Copy.
Bracer Phoenix hauling ass!
Gipsy to Command, do you have
a tactical scan of the hostile?
Assessing data
from their sensors.
We have it, Gipsy,
but it's still compiling.
No time.
Can you locate the brains?
Hostile's central brain mass
is heavily armored.
Your weapons
won't be able to penetrate.
What about a secondary brain?
This son of a bitch
have one of those?
Hostile has
three secondary brains,
one for each component Kaiju.
Sending intel.
Package confirmed for Saber Athena!
Confirmed for Bracer Phoenix.
All right, team,
follow my lead and stay alert!
Fire up some of that Fury tech
Liwen grabbed us?
Read my mind, partner.
Yeah!
- Eject!
- Damage detected.
Eject! Eject!
All pilots, eject!
Amara!
Warning.
Neural load exceeding limit.
- Hey!
- Warning.
- Neural load exceeding limit.
- Nate! Nate!
Stay with me! Stay with me!
Get up! Nate!
Pilot down!
Get up from that,
you pile of junk!
Bye!
Liwen! Is there anything
you can do to help?
- I need more time!
- We don't have any!
- If the hostile reaches Mount Fuji...
- Understood.
Not gonna let that happen.
Jake, you can't operate
Gipsy without a copilot!
The strain will tear your mind apart!
What do we do now?
Regroup with the others.
Amara!
Gipsy Avenger,
this is Amara Namani!
- Stand by for assist.
- Amara, don't.
- You won't make it.
- I'm gonna!
Don't! Don't!
I told you.
Since when do I listen?
Amara, you're up.
What are you doing?
Getting the hell
out of your way.
You got this, brother.
Ejection sequence initiated.
Ejection sequence successful.
- You ready for this, smallie?
- One way to find out.
Okay.
Stand by, Command.
Initiating neural handshake.
Establishing neural link.
Come on.
Yeah, that was supposed
to be epic, but it wasn't.
- Definitely not.
- Warning.
Cascade failure.
Multiple systems offline.
- Reboot!
- Okay, okay, I'm on it.
Command to Gipsy.
Hostile is...
two kilometers from the summit
of Mount Fuji and closing fast!
Gottlieb, do you have enough
fuel left in your thrusters
- to launch us into the atmosphere?
- The atmosphere?
- Yeah.
- Possibly, but there won't be
- enough to slow your reentry.
- We don't need to slow down.
We're gonna drop Gipsy
right on top of that thing.
I just ejected my escape pod.
Yeah. We'll have to use mine.
Jake, there's only one thruster
with enough fuel remaining.
- Sending location.
- All right, checking.
We're too far away.
We're not gonna make it.
Gipsy Avenger!
Transport inbound!
Remote systems are online.
Sending help!
Scrapper!
I've located the thruster pod!
Stand by!
Come on, come on!
Move them little legs!
The thruster's way too strong.
There's no way
we can hold on to it!
Liwen, what do you got?
I can weld it to your hand.
I upgraded Scrapper's weapons.
Nice. I was actually
gonna do that.
- No, you wasn't.
- Yes, I was.
We only got one shot at this.
Yeah! Then let's make it count.
- I'm stuck!
- Stay there!
You're an extra ton
we can drop on that thing!
- She's coming apart!
- Almost there!
- We're drifting off course!
- Use the plasma cannon!
Disengaging safety protocol!
Plasma cannon engaged.
Warning.
Exceeding structural limits.
- It's working!
- Structural failure.
Hold on!
Come on! Come on!
Target locked!
Jake, Amara, you need to eject!
Disconnect!
Amara, disconnect!
I will catch you!
I promise!
Come on!
I've got you.
Gipsy to Command, we're getting
the hell out of here!
Escape pod failure.
No. No, no, no!
I'm sorry, smallie.
For what?
We got to save the world.
Your dad would be proud.
Ah!
- Scrapper! Ah!
- Ah!
Get over here! Hurry up!
Move! We have to go!
20 kilometers to impact.
Get out of there!
Go! Go!
We're in!
Close the door!
- Hang on!
- I am hanging on!
Hang tighter!
No! No!
Okay, you know what?
Plan B. Always a plan B.
Anyone who's listening,
this is Ranger Lambert.
Be advised, we just
caught ourselves a Newt.
Copy that.
There he is.
I'm glad
you're still okay, man.
You, too, brother.
I knew you could do it.
Well, I had a lot of help.
- Nice work, Ranger Namani.
- Thank you, sir.
- Never seen snow before.
- So out of all the things
to notice right now,
you're noticing snow?
Big, dead Kaiju is just,
is right there,
- and I'm not sure if...
- Okay, okay, all right.
Is this the part
where you're gonna give me
one of those
big, dumb speeches, 'cause...
Did everyone think it was dumb
or is that just your opinion...
Just be honest, how many times
did you practice that in front
- of the mirror?
- It was motivational.
- Okay.
- You can be whoever you want to be.
Oh!
- Fire!
- Okay. Oh, now you want to play that?
I'm a natural at this.
- No, you're not a natural because...
- Ha!
Give me a break.
I've never done this before.
There you go. Boom!
We did it!
You think this is over, huh?
You think you've saved
your crappy little world?
We're gonna keep coming!
We are never going to stop,
and sooner or later,
your luck is going to run out!
Nah.
The things in your head?
The Precursors?
Tell them we're not afraid.
Tell 'em, next time,
they won't need to worry
about coming for us,
'cause we're gonna
come for them.